<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Vicky Lim</title>
    <link>https://vickylim.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Vicky Lim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Vicky Lim</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 12:55:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vickylim.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intentions for 2025</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2025/01/01/intentions-for-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 12:55:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2025/01/01/intentions-for-2025/</guid>
      <description>Prioritize connecting with other people. Meet new people (attend numerous meetups), maintain existing friendships (be responsive to messages, send mail, suggest plans, welcome everyone into my home), and always make the trek, no matter the distance or weather or mood, esp. if I committed in advance. Take a nap beforehand if I need it. MAYBE engage more on Instagram, but Idk about that one (probably not).
Express more encouragement by recognizing positive efforts made by friends and colleagues, as opposed to noticing immediately what could be fixed or reacting with judgments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After three months of strength training</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2024/12/24/after-three-months-of-strength-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 23:57:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2024/12/24/after-three-months-of-strength-training/</guid>
      <description>I remember feeling like such a poser wearing my Adidas track jacket while riding the train in September &amp;lsquo;21. It made me look athletic, but I was self-conscious because I did not do any kind of exercise at all.
Next thing I know, it&amp;rsquo;s September &amp;lsquo;24 and I&amp;rsquo;m walking around with a gym bag 3x a week so that I can go train at Starting Strength. I throw in my favorite 100% cotton t-shirt, pants, water bottle, one pair of shoes for squats and another for deadlifts, my training journal, and other misc items (still looking for a &amp;ldquo;lucky troll doll&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beginning of my winter break</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2024/12/15/the-beginning-of-my-winter-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 23:50:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2024/12/15/the-beginning-of-my-winter-break/</guid>
      <description>So, it&amp;rsquo;s the first weekend of my winter break and I&amp;rsquo;m off for three weeks! I&amp;rsquo;m not going anywhere. My only plan is to &amp;ldquo;do nothing&amp;rdquo; and see what happens 🤠
1 Yesterday, I attended the first meeting of the Classics Book Club to preview Wuthering Heights with 18 other people. I felt quite at ease in the library, sitting around a table with other readers, feeling like a student. It&amp;rsquo;s been so long since I&amp;rsquo;ve joined a book club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling more at home</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2024/08/23/feeling-more-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 22:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2024/08/23/feeling-more-at-home/</guid>
      <description>I have lived in the same one-bedroom for over a decade now and spent many of those years coming in to sleep and going back out for another day of work. This routine was often followed by an evening class, a late-night concert, a hangout, or getting sidetracked by errands while on my long commute home. I never made enough time to take care of my space, so it was nonstop dusty and I was always disgusted by the clutter and piles of actual trash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Solstice 2022</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2022/12/21/winter-solstice-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 21:44:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2022/12/21/winter-solstice-2022/</guid>
      <description>I started the day busy with my backpack, trying to decide what to bring with nowhere to go. I&amp;rsquo;m taking a couple weeks off work for a winter break and determined not to squander any minute. I could venture out of my neighborhood, walking 10-20k steps, visiting libraries and museums, and either finish reading the remaining volumes of In Search of Lost Time or study the books I&amp;rsquo;ve collected this year on a shelf dedicated to physical health, sports, and meditation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Chinese in 2021</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2021/12/31/learning-chinese-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 22:00:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2021/12/31/learning-chinese-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Out of nowhere on Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day this year, after one of my regular conversation practice sessions with my French tutor, I began searching online for Mandarin resources. In hindsight, I was probably looking for a distraction out of my intermediate plateau with French, where I am still struggling to stretch from B1 to B2. One click led to another until I decided to order Assimil: Le chinois, sealing my commitment that it will be the next language I learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intentions for this blog</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2021/12/03/intentions-for-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 14:36:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2021/12/03/intentions-for-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>There is no blank page, Céline Sciamma wrote on the trading card I made of her. I held this mantra since February, 2020, the month before the start of the pandemic, and I still kept struggling to write.
To diminish my dread, I find it helpful to begin with either an epigraph or a few notes on what I aim to accomplish, so here is what I would like for this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
