<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>intentions on Vicky Lim</title>
    <link>https://vickylim.com/tags/intentions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in intentions on Vicky Lim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Vicky Lim</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:08:59 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vickylim.com/tags/intentions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intentions for 2026</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2026/01/01/intentions-for-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:08:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2026/01/01/intentions-for-2026/</guid>
      <description>Placeholder post because it is an hour before midnight and I just wanted to timestamp this before the first day of the year is over. In the meantime, I have only ONE focus for this new year—to cut down on dining out, takeout, and any deliveries by at least 50% (ideally more) compared to last year. I am reading the Art of Eating In by Cathy Erway right now to learn more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intentions for 2025</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2025/01/01/intentions-for-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 12:55:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2025/01/01/intentions-for-2025/</guid>
      <description>Prioritize connecting with other people. Meet new people (attend numerous meetups, community events), maintain existing friendships (be responsive to messages, send mail, suggest plans, welcome everyone into my home), and always make the trek, no matter the distance or weather or mood, esp. if I committed in advance.
Express more encouragement by recognizing positive efforts made by friends and colleagues, as opposed to noticing immediately what could be fixed or reacting with judgments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intentions for this blog</title>
      <link>https://vickylim.com/2021/12/03/intentions-for-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 14:36:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylim.com/2021/12/03/intentions-for-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>There is no blank page, Céline Sciamma wrote on the trading card I made of her. I held this mantra since February, 2020, the month before the start of the pandemic, and I still kept struggling to write.
To diminish my dread, I find it helpful to begin with either an epigraph or a few notes on what I aim to accomplish, so here is what I would like for this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
